{
  "Items": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "front": "あ",
      "back": "A"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "front": "い",
      "back": "I"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "front": "う",
      "back": "U"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "front": "え",
      "back": "E"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "front": "お",
      "back": "O"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "front": "か",
      "back": "KA"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "front": "き",
      "back": "KI"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "front": "く",
      "back": "KU"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "front": "け",
      "back": "KE"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "front": "こ",
      "back": "KO"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "front": "さ",
      "back": "SA"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "front": "し",
      "back": "SHI"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "front": "す",
      "back": "SU"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "front": "せ",
      "back": "SE"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "front": "そ",
      "back": "SO"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "front": "た",
      "back": "TA"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "front": "ち",
      "back": "CHI"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "front": "つ",
      "back": "TSU"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "front": "て",
      "back": "TE"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "front": "と",
      "back": "TO"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "front": "な",
      "back": "NA"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "front": "に",
      "back": "NI"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "front": "ぬ",
      "back": "NU"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "front": "ね",
      "back": "NE"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "front": "の",
      "back": "NO"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "front": "は",
      "back": "HA"
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "front": "ひ",
      "back": "HI"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "front": "ふ",
      "back": "FU"
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "front": "へ",
      "back": "HE"
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "front": "ほ",
      "back": "HO"
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "front": "ま",
      "back": "MA"
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "front": "み",
      "back": "MI"
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "front": "む",
      "back": "MU"
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "front": "め",
      "back": "ME"
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "front": "も",
      "back": "MO"
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "front": "や",
      "back": "YA"
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "front": "ゆ",
      "back": "YU"
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "front": "よ",
      "back": "YO"
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "front": "ら",
      "back": "RA"
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "front": "り",
      "back": "RI"
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "front": "る",
      "back": "RU"
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "front": "れ",
      "back": "RE"
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "front": "ろ",
      "back": "RO"
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "front": "わ",
      "back": "WA"
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "front": "を",
      "back": "WO"
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "front": "ん",
      "back": "N"
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "front": "が",
      "back": "GA"
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "front": "ぎ",
      "back": "GI"
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "front": "ぐ",
      "back": "GU"
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "front": "げ",
      "back": "GE"
    },
    {
      "id": 51,
      "front": "ご",
      "back": "GO"
    },
    {
      "id": 52,
      "front": "ざ",
      "back": "ZA"
    },
    {
      "id": 53,
      "front": "じ",
      "back": "JI"
    },
    {
      "id": 54,
      "front": "ず",
      "back": "ZU"
    },
    {
      "id": 55,
      "front": "ぜ",
      "back": "ZE"
    },
    {
      "id": 56,
      "front": "ぞ",
      "back": "ZO"
    },
    {
      "id": 57,
      "front": "だ",
      "back": "DA"
    },
    {
      "id": 58,
      "front": "ぢ",
      "back": "JI"
    },
    {
      "id": 59,
      "front": "づ",
      "back": "DZU"
    },
    {
      "id": 60,
      "front": "で",
      "back": "DE"
    },
    {
      "id": 61,
      "front": "ど",
      "back": "DO"
    },
    {
      "id": 62,
      "front": "ば",
      "back": "BA"
    },
    {
      "id": 63,
      "front": "び",
      "back": "BI"
    },
    {
      "id": 64,
      "front": "ぶ",
      "back": "BU"
    },
    {
      "id": 65,
      "front": "べ",
      "back": "BE"
    },
    {
      "id": 66,
      "front": "ぼ",
      "back": "BO"
    },
    {
      "id": 67,
      "front": "ぱ",
      "back": "PA"
    },
    {
      "id": 68,
      "front": "ぴ",
      "back": "PI"
    },
    {
      "id": 69,
      "front": "ぷ",
      "back": "PU"
    },
    {
      "id": 70,
      "front": "ぺ",
      "back": "PE"
    },
    {
      "id": 71,
      "front": "ぽ",
      "back": "PO"
    },
    {
      "id": 72,
      "front": "きゃ",
      "back": "KYA"
    },
    {
      "id": 73,
      "front": "きゅ",
      "back": "KYU"
    },
    {
      "id": 74,
      "front": "きょ",
      "back": "KYO"
    },
    {
      "id": 75,
      "front": "しゃ",
      "back": "SHA"
    },
    {
      "id": 76,
      "front": "しゅ",
      "back": "SHU"
    },
    {
      "id": 77,
      "front": "しょ",
      "back": "SHO"
    },
    {
      "id": 78,
      "front": "ちゃ",
      "back": "CHA"
    },
    {
      "id": 79,
      "front": "ちゅ",
      "back": "CHU"
    },
    {
      "id": 80,
      "front": "ちょ",
      "back": "CHO"
    },
    {
      "id": 81,
      "front": "にゃ",
      "back": "NYA"
    },
    {
      "id": 82,
      "front": "にゅ",
      "back": "NYU"
    },
    {
      "id": 83,
      "front": "にょ",
      "back": "NYO"
    },
    {
      "id": 84,
      "front": "ひゃ",
      "back": "HYA"
    },
    {
      "id": 85,
      "front": "ひゅ",
      "back": "HYU"
    },
    {
      "id": 86,
      "front": "ひょ",
      "back": "HYO"
    },
    {
      "id": 87,
      "front": "みゃ",
      "back": "MYA"
    },
    {
      "id": 88,
      "front": "みゅ",
      "back": "MYU"
    },
    {
      "id": 89,
      "front": "みょ",
      "back": "MYO"
    },
    {
      "id": 90,
      "front": "りゃ",
      "back": "RYA"
    },
    {
      "id": 91,
      "front": "りゅ",
      "back": "RYU"
    },
    {
      "id": 92,
      "front": "りょ",
      "back": "RYO"
    },
    {
      "id": 93,
      "front": "ぎゃ",
      "back": "GYA"
    },
    {
      "id": 94,
      "front": "ぎゅ",
      "back": "GYU"
    },
    {
      "id": 95,
      "front": "ぎょ",
      "back": "GYO"
    },
    {
      "id": 96,
      "front": "じゃ",
      "back": "JA"
    },
    {
      "id": 97,
      "front": "じゅ",
      "back": "JU"
    },
    {
      "id": 98,
      "front": "じょ",
      "back": "JO"
    },
    {
      "id": 99,
      "front": "ぢゃ",
      "back": "JA"
    },
    {
      "id": 100,
      "front": "ぢゅ",
      "back": "JU"
    },
    {
      "id": 101,
      "front": "ぢょ",
      "back": "JO"
    },
    {
      "id": 102,
      "front": "びゃ",
      "back": "BYA"
    },
    {
      "id": 103,
      "front": "びゅ",
      "back": "BYU"
    },
    {
      "id": 104,
      "front": "びょ",
      "back": "BYO"
    },
    {
      "id": 105,
      "front": "ぴゃ",
      "back": "PYA"
    },
    {
      "id": 106,
      "front": "ぴゅ",
      "back": "PYU"
    },
    {
      "id": 107,
      "front": "ぴょ",
      "back": "PYO"
    }
  ]
}